It's cute.
かわいいじゃん
Are you nervous?
緊張してるの?
Peace, camera.
ピースしてよ、カメラ
Peace, peace.
ピース、ピース
Try peace.
ピースしてごらん
It seems like you're forcing yourself to do it.
無理やりやってるみたいじゃん
Peace.
ピースして
i don't know?
知らない?
Yeah.
うん
Have you never understood?
分かったことないの?
Didn't you buy the blue one yourself?
ブルーだって自分で買ってないの?
Have you ever pitched?
ピッチしたことあるんでしょ?
Yes, there is.
あるよね
Yeah?
ええ?
It doesn't exist, right?
無くないでしょ?
There is, right?
あるでしょ?
Pay the money properly.
ちゃんとお金払うんだ
I know exactly.
ちゃんと知ってるよ
Isn't it okay?
いいんでしょ?
Does the store have bread?
店パン入ってるの?
Black pants?
黒パンツか
You're always wearing black underneath.
下にいつも黒とかあんた
Is there a lot of black?
黒多いの?
Please take this off.
脱いでくれよ、これ
What is this?
これ何?
one piece?
ワンピース?
Look.
見て
Let's take it off.
脱いでくれっていこうよ
difference
さ
Wake up and move
っ き起きて動いてく
Ru.
る
Don't you feel it here?
ここ で感じないの?
It's been a while since I slept.
久々に寝てる
You're sleeping, aren't you?
寝てるよね
Chiquitabet.
チキタベット
It seems like an adult.
大人っぽいよね
For a 15 year old.
15歳にしては
It's very productive.
生ませてるな、すごく
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
You got a lot of crap.
ワンカスいっぱいついたよね
hey.
ね
Full of one-liners.
ワンカスだらけ
Show me, show me.
見せて、見せて
Okay, I like this.
いいよ、これ好きなんだよ
Wancas.
ワンカス
Open it yourself.
自分で開いて
Do you touch it yourself?
自分で触ったりするの?
yeah?
ん?
Stay open, like that.
開いててね、そうやって
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
Isn't it okay to be loud?
結構声出してもいいんじゃないですか?
I say it's close to my feet
足近いって言っちゃう
from.
から
Are you embarrassed?
恥 ずかしいの?
Open it.
開いて
what happened?
どうしたの?
It's here.
ここだよね
Hey, what's wrong?
ほら、どうしたの?
You're doing a great job.
すごい力やってるじゃん
Finish it properly.
ちゃんと仕上げて
This one too.
これ、こっちも
Please finish it.
仕上げててね
Look.
ほ ら
Are you spinning something?
何か回してるの?
You're doing a great job.
すごい力やってるじゃん
It's gone, right?
いっちゃったでしょ?
yeah?
ん?
It's gone, right?
いっちゃったでしょ?
I have to say this.
言わないとダメだよ、これ
Did you see it?
見た?
May I ask you something?
ちょっと聞いてもらってもいいかな?
Even if it's a little.
少々しても
Haven't you seen it yet?
まだ見たことないの?
Why are you not good at it?
なんで苦手?
This is how you do it, right?
こうやってできるでしょ?
Is this enough?
もうこれいい?
Can't you?
できない?
Okay, I'll put it in.
よいしょ、入れちゃうよ
good?
いい?
Is it okay to include it?
入れていいでしょ?
I'll put it in.
入れるじゃん
Put it in.
入れて
Hold your legs and look at me.
足持ってて、こっち見て
Feels good.
気持ちいい
what happened?
どうしたの?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
what happened?
どうしたの?
Huh?
あれ?
Have you ever said that?
って言ったことないの?
Isn't that a lie?
嘘でしょ?
You pushed it harder than that, right?
それ以上張ったじゃん、ちゃんと
Oh, does it hurt?
あ、 痛いの?
You can put it in.
入れていいからさ
Turn around.
後 ろ 向いて
Turn around and try again.
後ろ向いて、また張ってみて
Is this the way to go?
これ、行き?
Amazing power.
すごい力
yeah?
ん?
Does it hurt?
痛いの?
Can't move?
動けない?
Does it hurt just by putting it in?
入れただけで痛いの?
You can go.
行っていいよ
If it's more than that, you can't go, right?
それ以上だったら、行けないでしょ?
Your feet?
足を?
When I lift my feet, I see what's here.
足上げると、ここが何か
Is it a girl?
少女なの?
Right?
そうでしょ?
I spent it.
過ごしたよ
Some of the things we put together.
出し合った中には
Maybe we can have a baby.
赤ちゃんできちゃうかもね